<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IntelliRoast</string>
    <string name="lightRoast">Light Roast</string>
    <string name="mediumRoast">Medium Roast</string>
    <string name="darkRoast">Dark Roast</string>
    <string name="select">Choose</string>
    <string name="lightRoastDescription">Light roasts are light brown in color, with a light body
        and no oil on the surface of the beans. Light roasts have a toasted grain taste and pronounced
        acidity. The origin flavors of the bean are retained to a greater extent than in darker
        roasted coffees. Light roasts also retain most of the caffeine from the coffee bean. Some
        common roast names within the Light Roast category are Light City, Half City, Cinnamon Roast
        (roasted to just before first crack), and New England Roast (a popular roast in the northeastern
        United States, roasted to first crack).</string>
    <string name="mediumRoastDescription">Medium roasted coffees are medium brown in color with more
        body than light roasts. Like the lighter roasts, they have no oil on the bean surfaces.
        However, medium roasts lack the grainy taste of the light roasts, exhibiting more balanced
        flavor, aroma, and acidity. Caffeine is somewhat decreased, but there is more caffeine than
        in darker roasts. Common roast names within the Medium Roast level include Regular Roast,
        American Roast (the traditional roast in the eastern United States, roasted to the end of the
        first crack), City Roast (medium brown, a typical roast throughout the United States), and
        Breakfast Roast.</string>
    <string name="darkRoastDescription">Dark roasted coffees are dark brown in color, like chocolate,
        or sometimes almost black. They have a sheen of oil on the surface, which is usually evident
        in the cup when the dark roast coffee is brewed. The coffee’s origin flavors are eclipsed by
        the flavors of the roasting process. The coffee will generally have a bitter and smoky or even
        burnt taste. The amount of caffeine is substantially decreased. Some of the more popular
        designations for a dark roast include French Roast, Italian Roast, Espresso Roast, Continental
        Roast, New Orleans Roast, and Spanish Roast. Many dark roasts are used for espresso blends.</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="disc">Discoverable</string>
    <string name="paired">Get Paired Devices</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect to IntelliRoast</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect from IntelliRoast</string>
    <string name="eject">Eject beans (emergency use only)</string>
    <string name="stopRoast">Stop and cool down the current roast</string>
    <string name="devOptions">Development Options</string>
    <string name="devOptionsDescription">Below are current roast readings. You can also manually
        adjust fan speed and heating element power.</string>
</resources>
